

leninesteban98@outlook.co



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



portfolio-lp-a1388.web.app/



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



twitter.com/4fourlp? t=jgeNASSGNviB9dRdULaQB Q&s=09



github.com/Lenin4lp

SKILLS

JavaScript

нтмі

CSS

React

Front-End

IDIOMAS

Spanish

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

English

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

INTERESTS

Mobile Dev

Web Dev

Videogames Dev

Lenin Patiño

Software Developer

I am a highly motivated Ecuadorian software developer with a specialization in web development. I hold a degree in Software Development Technology and have successfully developed multiple websites. I am passionate about learning and always strive to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies in the field.

FORMATION

Advanced Technology in Software Development Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Tesis

 Developed a virtual tour for Lev Vygotsky School

EXPERIENCIE

Administrative Assistant Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Achievements/Responsabilities

- Auxiliar administrativo
- Logística
- Trabajo en Equipo

Contacto: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

ORGANIZATIONS

Nebuluz (06/2023 - Present)

Co-fundador

CERTIFICATES

SUDEN Certificate: Expert in computer, mobile phone, and printer repair. (04/2023 - 05/2023)

SUDEN Certificate: Technical specialization (04/2023 - 05/2023)

SUDEN Certificate: International Technical Expert (04/2023 - 04/2023)

PERSONAL PROYECTS

E-Commerce Website (03/2023 - Present)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Top graduate of the Software Development program

Sangolquí, Ecuador

Fast Food Restaurant



\searrow

leninesteban98@outlook.co



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



portfolio-lp-a1388.web.app/



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



twitter.com/4fourlp? t=jgeNASSGNviB9dRdULaQB Q&s=09



github.com/Lenin4lp

COMPETENCIAS

JavaScript

HTML



React

Front-End

IDIOMAS

Español

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

Inglés

Competencia Profesional Plena

INTERESES

Desarrollo móvil

Desarrollo web

Desarrollo de videojuegos

Lenin Patiño

Desarrollador de Software

Soy un desarrollador de Software ecuatoriano altamente motivado, especializado en desarrollo web. Poseo un título de Tecnología Superior en Desarrollo de Software y he creado exitosamente varias aplicaciones web. Me apasiona aprender y siempre me esfuerzo por mantenerme actualizado con las últimas tecnologías en el campo.

Sangolquí, Ecuador

Fast Food Restaurant

FORMACIÓN

Tecnología Superior en Desarrollo de Software Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Tesis

 Desarrollo de un tour virtual para el colegio Lev Vygotsky

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Auxiliar Administrativo Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Logros/Funciones

- Auxiliar administrativo
- Logística
- Trabajo en Equipo

Contacto: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

ORGANIZACIONES

Nebuluz (06/2023 - Presente)

Co-fundador

CERTIFICADOS

Certificado SUDEN: Experto en reparación de computadoras, celulares e impresoras (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Certificado Suden: Especialidad Técnica (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Certificado SUDEN: Experto Técnico Internacional (04/2023 - 04/2023)

PROYECTOS PERSONALES

Sitio web E-Commerce (03/2023 - Presente)

LOGROS

Mejor egresado de la carrera de Desarrollo de Software